<file>
		<para>
				Latex-Suite attempts to provide a comprehensive set of tools to view, edit and
				compile LaTeX documents in Vim. Together, they provide tools starting from
				macros to speed up editing LaTeX documents to functions for forward searching
				.dvi documents. Latex-suite has been possible because of the contributions of
				many people. Please see <tag>latex-suite-credits</tag> for a list of people who have
				helped.
		</para>
		<para>
				Latex-suite is released under the Vim charityware license. For license and
				conditions of use look at <tag>copyright</tag>. Replace all occurences of ``Vim'' with
				``Latex-Suite''. The current copyright holders of Latex-Suite are Srinath
				Avadhanula and Mikolaj Machowski.
		</para>
		<para>
				Homepage: http://vim-latex.sourceforge.net
		</para>
		{Vi of course does not have any of this}<br/>
		<note>
			If you are viewing this in vim 6.0+, then the sections should
			appear folded (see <tag>folding</tag>). Use <tag>za</tag> to toggle back and
			forth between open and closed views.
		</note>
		<br/>
		<note>
			If the sections do not appear folded, press za in normal mode. This will
			fold up everything and it will be much easier to navigate.
		</note>

	<section>
		<sectiontitle>
			<name>OVERVIEW</name>
			<tag>latex-suite-overview</tag>
			<tag>latex-suite-alias1</tag>
		</sectiontitle>
		<link>latex-suite-optimal-settings</link>
		<br/>
		<para>
			Latex-Suite works best if you have the following settings in your ~/.vimrc:
		</para>
		<code>" this line is responsible for loading latex-suite when a .tex file is
" opened.
filetype plugin on
" for automatic indentation specific to LaTeX.
filetype indent on
		</code>
		<para>
			In addition, the following settings could go in your ~/.vim/ftplugin/tex.vim
			file:
		</para>
		<code>" this is mostly a matter of taste. but LaTeX looks good with just a bit
" of indentation.
set sw=2
" TIP: if you write your \label's as \label{fig:something}, then if you
" type in \ref{fig: and press &lt;C-n&gt; you will automatically cycle through 
" all the figure labels. Very useful!
set iskeyword+=:
" IMPORTANT: If you are a win32 user, then the following setting is
" necessary in order to have latex called correctly from within vim.
set shellslash 
		</code>
	</section>
</file>

<!--
vim: ts=2:sw=2
-->
