<file>
<option>
<name>b:Tex_Leader</name>
<name>g:Tex_Leader</name>
<desc>
    string (default empty) <br/>
    global <br/>
    {not in Vi} <br/>
    {not available when compiled without the |+statusline| or |+something|
    else feature} <par/>
    The mappings in latex-suite are by default prefixed with the back-tick
    character. For example, `/ inserts \frac{<++>}{<++>}<++> etc. You can change the
    prefix with the following setting.
    ',', '/', '`' are preferred values. '' or '\' will lead to a _lot_ of
    trouble.

    g:Tex_Leader is also used for visual mode mappings for fonts.
    <par/>
    <blockquote>This is some text which is supposed to be offset widthwise
        from the rest.</blockquote>
    <par/>
    This is a nested table:<par/>
    <table>
        <row>
            <col>11</col>
            <col>12</col>
            <col>13</col>
        </row>
        <row>
            <col>21</col>
            <col>
                <table>
                    <row>
                        <col>n.11</col><col>n.12</col>
                    </row>
                    <row>
                        <col>n.21</col><col>n.22</col>
                    </row>
                </table>
            </col>
            <col>23</col>
        </row>
        <row>
            <col>31</col>
            <col>32</col>
            <col>33</col>
        </row>
    </table>
    <par/>
    This is another table showing how column widths are calculated
    intelligently.
    <par/>
    <table>
        <row>
            <col>field</col>
            <col>meaning ~</col>
        </row>
        <row>
            <col>-</col> 
            <col>Left justify the item. The default is right justified
                when minwid is larger than the length of the item.</col> 
        </row>
        <row>
            <col>0</col>
            <col>Leading zeroes in numeric items. Overridden by '-'.</col> 
        </row>
        <row>
            <col>minwid</col>
            <col>Minimum width of the item, padding as set by '-' &amp; '0'.</col> 
        </row>
    </table>
    <br/>
    <code>" This is an example of a code block.
augroup LatexSuite
    au LatexSuiteInitPost :call MyFunc()
augroup END</code>
    <br/>
    <note>This is a note. <br/>And something else is here too. And something else is
        here too. And something else is here too. And something else is here
        too. And something else is here too. And something else is here too.
        And something else is here too. And something else is here too. And
        something else is here too. And something else is here too.
    </note>
    <par/>
    <list>
        <item>This is a list in an option. <br/>
            This is a line after a &lt;br/&gt; in an item.
        </item>
        <item>Item 2</item>
    </list>
</desc>
</option>
<list>
    <item>This is something. This is something. This is something. This is
        something. This is something. This is something. This is something.
        This is something. This is something. This is something. Item 1</item>
    <item>Item 2</item>
</list>
</file>
<!-- 
vim:et:sts=4 
-->
